Let's become treasure hunters!
We'll visit treasure vaults around the
world and attain riches and glory!
That sounds like fun!
Let's do it.
M-Me, too!
Yeah.
If it's us...
If it's the six of us,
we can definitely do it!
And we'll have one goal!
To be the best heroes in the world!
So someday, let's all go to
the imperial capital, Zebrudia.
Right, Krai?
Treasure hunters are considered
stars in the imperial capital.
They travel around the world to various
ruins, the so-called "treasure vaults,"
and collect the relics hidden inside.
It's a job where you risk your life
fighting monsters called "phantoms,"
but in return you can attain
vast riches and glory.
The clan "First Steps" is regarded
as very capable in the capital,
and today, they are holding interviews
for potential new members at a pub.
A clan is a collection of parties
that come together to assist one another.
There's a limit to how far
a solo hunter can go.
If you wish to set your sights high,
it's vital to get into a good party and
become stronger alongside your comrades.
Unfortunately, I failed to do that.
Hey, are you here to join a party as well?
Sorry to ask out of the blue.
Everyone's so on edge that
it's been putting me off.
But you looked more approachable.
My name is Rhuda Runebeck.
Rhuda Runebeck
Hunter level 3
I just recently got promoted to level 3.
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Krai Andrey.
It's nice to meet you, Rhuda.
A lot of people showed up, huh.
I've been going solo until now,
but I couldn't handle this treasure vault
called the "The White Wolf's Den."
That's why I was thinking
I could join some sort of part—
Don't make me laugh, girlie.
Who asked you?
You tried to take on the White
Wolf's Den at level 3?
This isn't a place for
amateur hunters like you!
Wha? Who are you calling an amateur?
Steps is a renowned clan,
even in the capital.
A level 3 may be considered
mid-grade anywhere else,
but here you're essentially a beginner.
You'd better go home
before you get hurt!
It said that they don't
care what level you are!
That's obviously just a formality!
What? You wanna go?!
What exactly did you have in mind?
This!
That's enough!
Take this any further,
and you'll lose any chance
of joining our clan!
Just kidding.
Hunters don't draw their
blades in the streets!
That's what I'm saying.
I slipped...
Wow...
Are these all hunters?
It looks like it.
It's so overwhelming.
I've never been to a place like this.
Have you?
This is my fifth time, I think.
That many?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
For hunters, skill is everything.
Those with talent can instantly make
a name for themselves and climb the ranks.
Those without cling to the
few chances they get.
Hey, Krai.
Which party is that flashy one?
That's quite the crowd.
Oh, those are the members of Ark Brave.
Of the ones recruiting,
they're the strongest party.
Ark Brave
They managed to complete a level 7
treasure vault with just six members.
So they're the elite of the elite.
A level 7?!
By the way, the person sitting
is their leader, Ark Rodin.
"Argent Thunderclap"
Ark Rodin
Hunter level 7
If he accepts you,
your success as a hunter is
essentially guaranteed,
but as far as I know, they have never accepted
a new member through one of these events.
Hmm.
So what about that desk
all the way in the back?
Nobody's there.
Hey, hey.
You really are clueless, aren't you?
What are...
You again?
Greg Zangief
Hunter level 4
Looks like I, the great Greg,
have no choice but to tell you.
No, thanks.
That's the table of the party that
originally founded First Steps.
He doesn't listen, does he...
That is, the Grievers.
The founders of this clan?!
The Grievers.
That's the alias of a party of youngsters
that came to this capital a few years ago.
With their overabundant and dazzling talent,
they made a name for themselves as one
of the top parties in the capital.
Their full name is "Grieving Souls."
Grieving Souls
That's the party of my childhood friends.
There's a rumor that for
the first time in years,
the Grievers are accepting new members.
That's the reason behind this huge turnout.
But look, that's not all.
Who are they?
Looks like solo hunters.
They're also aiming to join
the best—the Grievers.
There's nobody there, though.
Those rumors may have
been a bunch of hot air.
Hey! Where're the Grievers?
I don't have time for losers.
I came all the way here because
I heard the best would show up!
I'll be one of the strongest
hunters one day.
I've already made it to level 4!
And here I was, thinking of allowing the
capital's strongest party to recruit me.
Look at him talk.
No way... He's a higher level than me.
What's your problem?
You should know your place.
What?
Stop, Tino.
Don't make a scene.
It'll be over in one second.
I'll beat him out of here.
If my sister were here,
that's what she'd do.
I'm the one who deserves
to be in Grieving Souls.
I told you to stop.
The vice master told you
not to make a scene, either.
Just ignore the idiots.
Hey, who are you calling an idiot?
You, idiot!
I'm already busy, so don't
make more work for me!
Oh yeah, go for it!
Show him what the Steps are made of!
All right, all right!
Show her what you've got, ya dumb kid!
Who you calling dumb?!
Get 'em!
Hey!
Let's go outside.
We're dead if we get mixed up in this.
B-But...
Quickly.
Bring it on, then, shorty.
I can't go easy on you, though.
That's fine.
I'll figure out everything
else after I've killed you.
Just like my sister taught me.
I knew I shouldn't have come here.
You all ready?!
Yeah!
Give it all you've got!
Ready... Fight!
Umm...
What are you doing, Master?
How long have you been here?
Hey, Krai.
You're late.
Without you, the clan master
and leader of Grieving Souls,
we can't get anything started.
Clan master?
The leader... of the Grievers?
We are now in the golden age
of the treasure hunters!
Amid the sparkling talent on
display in the capital of Zebrudia,
there was one man who stood
out amongst all others!
His name is Krai Andrey.
This is an epic tale
full of glory and agony
of how he became renowned
for being the leader
of the strongest party he founded
with his childhood friends,
and also the master of the strongest clan!
"Thousand Tricks"
Krai Andrey
Hunter level 8
I think I'm going to puke...
First Steps... Like the first footstep, huh.
That's why they're known as Steps for short.
I see.
"Today, I Just Want to Go Home"...
Episode 01
Today, I Just Want to Go Home
Let This Grieving Soul Retire
It happened several years ago.
We had just come to the capital,
but we were finishing treasure vaults
suited for beginners in record speed.
Krai! Don't move a step!
Huh?
Krai!
This is the last one, right?
Huh? Uh, yeah.
That's our Krai!
Huh?
You were playing the bait, right?
I had no idea.
Hey, next you need to
watch me defeat one!
We all shared the same dream
of becoming treasure hunters.
Krai?
But the amount of talent
we had was not equal.
Sure.
Let's hurry, then.
Compared to the monstrous potential
the other five possessed,
I was exceedingly ordinary.
See! Let's rush through this to the end!
If I had stayed with them,
We're the best!
sooner or later,
I'd only be getting in their way.
Y-Yeah.
Krai!
Though they'd be kind
enough not to say anything.
What's wrong, Krai?
Which is why I had to make
that decision for myself.
To leave this party.
Thank you for everything.
I know all of you will go on
to become incredible hunters.
So I hope you'll understand.
Look, Krai.
Huh?
I've been thinking about this for a while.
We don't have a leader.
What? Yeah, I guess that's true.
You should do it.
Be our leader.
What?
That's a great idea!
I agree.
You're good at giving speeches, too.
Yeah.
Wait, um,
were you even listening to what I said?
That's how everything began,
and also how it ended.
For years now,
I've been the leader of this party
of my gifted childhood friends.
Always wishing that I could
retire from being a hunter.
I still can't believe this.
Krai is the clan master of First Steps.
But you know,
being late because you overslept
is a joke only you'd make.
Stay away from my master, fake pretty boy!
Your superficiality is contagious.
Superficiality?
Tino, you're too funny.
I guess you were observing the crowd by
going incognito among the common folk.
Yeah, no.
Ah, that's why you're
not wearing your uniform.
After you ordered us all
to be properly dressed!
Like I said, I just overslept.
I didn't have time to get ready.
If you say so.
Ark here isn't the only one.
Hunters basically never
listen to anything you say.
Master, this guy is really too insulting.
Let us strike his name from the clan roster!
What now?
Like I said, Tino. You're really too funny.
Her name is Tino Shade.
Shut up!
Tino Shade
Hunter level 4
Level 4.
Fake pretty boy!
A solo hunter affiliated with Steps.
Stop laughing!
And she's also an apprentice
to my childhood friend, Liz.
So how's it going?
Did you find a good candidate?
Well, we have enough members right now.
Oh!
If I said I had a potential
new member in mind,
would you take them in?
I would. I trust you.
What!?
Slow down, Ark!
This is out of nowhere!
Only one person, though.
Anyone at all?
As long as you recommend them, sure.
That's Ark for you.
Not only is he handsome, he's also generous.
Well, then...
Forcing them onto us...
Master...
Being chosen is such an honor,
but I've already set my
heart on joining you.
So joining that fake boy's party's a bit...
Hey, you!
Let me go!
Not him again.
Tino, it's fine.
Uf you sho deshperatey wan me an beg,
I guesh I could shink about it!
Shut up, idiot!
Hey, you.
You said you were a level 4, right?
But you're not affiliated with any party?
It's none of your damn business!
What's your name?
Gilbert.
Gilbert Bush
Hunter level 4
Gilbert Bush.
Gilbert of the Purgatorial Sword!
Purgatorial Sword, huh?
He won't be an asset immediately,
but once Ark and the others train him...
Hm?
I am terrible at judging people.
Anyone I pick will be based on luck.
Fine then, Gilbert.
I shall recommend you to Ark.
On one condition.
Which is?
What do you think is the most
important thing for a hunter?
It's to not lose.
If you lack strength,
you will eventually put
your party into danger.
So I need you to show me
your ability to not lose.
By the way... since becoming a hunter
I haven't lost a single time.
What?!
Wow! I knew it!
You're so amazing, Master!
Amazing!
Well, I simply have never
been in a proper fight.
This is to every single one
of you here right now!
I will recommend whoever manages
to get this relic to Ark Brave!
Is he okay?
Where is Master's ring?
Wait, what?
No!
By the way, that ring is actually a relic.
Whoever gets it can keep it, so good luck!
Rhuda and The Great Greg.
Who, me?
Maybe we'll see each other again.
Y-Yes. See you later.
Later, Ark.
Yes. Later.
You're in my way!
Right, then.
I'm going home.
Krai, you made the front page news.
First Steps Clan House
"Huge Brawl Breaks Out at
Ark Brave's Recruitment."
It ended with the venue getting blown up.
Were any civilians hurt?
Luckily, there seem to
have been no injuries.
First Steps Vice Clan Master
Eva Renfied
But the Explorers'
Association wants a word.
Seriously?
Did Ark say anything?
He read the article and laughed.
He really is easy-going.
Great, then put the pub's repair
bill onto Ark's account.
And please have him go to the
Explorers' Association as well.
You really do rely on Ark too much.
The Explorers' Association specifically
asked for you to be there.
Knowing Branch Manager Gark,
if I don't go, he'll come to see me instead.
I don't want to go outside
without an escort.
My disguise relic was broken, too.
The Reversible Face.
Reversible Face!
Equip! And activate!
Just like that, a visual change!
Oh, yes!
You can have any face you want!
It's a real revolution!
Reversible Face
Reversible Face!
Don't leave home without it!
*Please make sure to consult the user guide and use responsibly.
No one's going to attack you at this hour.
It's never happened to you,
so it's easy for you to say.
I guess I have no choice.
I'm going.
I am so...
So sorry for all the trouble I caused!
It wasn't on purpose!
It wasn't out of malice!
And I made sure that no
civilians would get hurt!
Honestly, I was in a bind myself!
Not like I could have stopped that chaos!
Once it started, the only
way was to let it play out!
Hey, stop trying to rush through this.
Explorers' Association Zebrudia Branch Manager
Gark Welter
The only damage was to the building, right?
So it's okay, right?!
Better property than people!
Nobody has sent in a complaint yet,
the owner of that pub
hall and I go way back,
and they're a super nice person,
so it's fine! They'll forgive us!
And I want ice cream!
Krai, please calm down.
Also, you don't have to scold him that hard.
I haven't even scolded him
at all yet, but whatever.
Take this, Krai.
Even if nobody has officially complained,
a clan like First Steps needs to
set an example for other hunters.
If you get off scot free, it'll be no good.
You mean a chore?
Don't call it that.
The Explorers' Association,
the Association for short,
gets all sorts of jobs for hunters.
Some of those jobs
pay so little,
have such short deadlines,
or are so stupidly difficult
that nobody will do them.
Hunters respectfully call these
types of jobs "chores."
This puts me in quite a predicament!
As an ex-hunter yourself,
surely you understand.
Hmm?
Well, I'm not saying that
I won't accept this.
You've done so much for me, so I'll do it.
But if I may say one thing.
Our misstep this time
wasn't even that bad.
I feel like his provoke
skill leveled up again.
Hmph.
Pick one.
Yes, sir.
I'll try to pick an easy
one and pass it on to Ark.
Treasure vault levels of 5, 4, 5, 7, 6...
Found one! A level 3!
I'll take this one, Gark.
Put me on corpse retrieval duty.
That's a rescue mission, Krai.
You shouldn't make light of it.
He really is always full of energy, huh?
He's fine just as he is.
Nothing's changed.
And then...
He went ahead and chose the most
dangerous looking mission.
What? Ark's not here?
That's right!
The fake pretty boy was summoned
by some nobles or something.
He said he'd be gone for a while.
I see.
So nobody's here.
Master...
Huh?
Oh!
You got the ring!
That's right!
I didn't want anyone else
to get their hands on your ring.
Can I really keep this?
Yeah.
It's just a Shooting Ring, though.
Yay!
So hey, are you free right now?
I am!
I've never been more free in my entire life!
Which is why I've been waiting for you!
That's perfect.
I got a quest from the
Explorers' Association.
Oh, jeez.
Hounding Chain
All yours, Silver.
Master.
This is the biggest shock of my entire life.
My maidenly heart is in tatters.
I never would have imagined you'd
do something this terrible.
I've been deceived.
A bait-and-switch.
I never deceived you,
nor did I pull a bait-and-switch.
In all honesty,
all I wanted to do was go
have some ice cream with you.
Instead, you're making me do this
unprecedented crappy chore.
The compensation is minimal,
the contractual binding time is super long...
I can't find a single good thing about this.
Who the hell would ever take this on?
Yes, yes.
You're so right.
Master, I'm still a level 4.
There's no way I can rescue
five people all alone!
Yes, yes.
You're so right.
I know you send us on these missions
where we brush with death as a
way to make us all stronger,
but please don't get carried
away with the Spartan training!
Yes, yes.
You're so righ...
Close to death?
On a level 3?
I see.
You're saying you don't
want to go all alone.
Y-Yes!
But you know, if you came
along, that would be...
This is at the White Wolf's Den, right?
Huh?
A girl shouldered with misfortune.
Will this impromptu party of four be
able to face this mystery job
that everybody shied away from?
Find out in the next episode!
Don't miss it!
By: Tino Shade & Wall Spaghetti Party
My master, also known as Thousand
Tricks, forced this on me.
Urgent request!
We have to go to the White
Wolf's. Danger is dangerous!
Treasure vault!
Hastily assembled!
Wall spaghetti party!
We'll go all out!
Until the end?!
Is everybody ready?!
Uh, yes.
Next time on Let This Grieving Soul...
...Retire!
Episode 02
I Want to Leave It to Tino and Take It Easy
You're on, Master!
"I Want to Leave It to Tino and Take It Easy."